Hello Hello, how am I from the
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте как я из
city of Khmelnitsk, where are you from? From the city of
города Хмельницке Вы откуда Из города
Surgut, a
Сургут понял
Ukrainian understands no. It’s strange that there are a lot of
украинец нет Странно там очень много
Ukrainians there. Well, you don’t look a bit like
украинцев Да ну вы немножко не похожи на
Ukraine, you are Russian by
Украин вы кто по
nationality.
национальности
And where are your relatives
русский А откуда родственники
from all over the world? Well, where are the souls of the Bausch
родом со всего мира Ну откуда душ бауш
grandfathers and two
дедушки и две
grandmothers
бабушки
?  - probably from the
м где-то наверное с
Krasnodar region, both grandmothers, both grandfathers Well, I
Краснодара обе бабушки оба дедушки Ну я
myself was born in Kazakhstan, they
сам родился в Казахстане они туда
came there with Cossack regiments I don’t know
приехали с казачьими полками Я не знаю
from But with the Cossack regiments all this is well,
от А с казачьими полками всё то это ну
not a Russian, not a Muscovite understood Yeah, the
не русский не москаль понял
Cossacks didn’t like the Muscovite either Yes, the
Угу казаки тоже москаля не любили Да
Donets are Kuban people
донцы кубанцы
there, Yeah  after 917, when the Russian
там Угу после 917 года Когда Российская
Empire collapsed, they made a Cossack
империя развалила сделали там казачью
Republic there, where was it in the
Республику было где оно на
Kuban? No, I’m from Kazakhstan, what do you have to do with it,
Кубани Нет я сам с Казахстана мне причём
you’re relatives from the Kuban, you
это же вы родственники с Кубани вы
said you came to Kazakhstan Well, apparently you
сказали приехали в Казахстан Ну видимо
came from there, yes, well, I’m saying yes, that is,
оттуда приехали да ну то я же говорю да
your relatives are against
то есть ваши родственники против Моск ле
They fought in Moscow Yes, Lenin then captured this
этих воевали Да Ленин потом захватил эту
Kuban Republic Uh-huh yes So it’s
кубанскую Республику Угу да Так что
normal, well, I see that you have a flight
нормально ну я же вижу что у вас полету
but you didn’t disguise it, well, really, it’s not a katsap But
но вы не маскали ну реально не кацап А
so yes, great Well, I have the right to
вот так вот Да отлично Ну имею право на
life Apparently yes Atsa Also has the right to
жизнь Видимо да Аца Тоже имеет право на
life in which Muscovites also have the right, in
жизнь в чём москвичи тоже имеют право в
what fun it has And what I don’t know What does it have to do with
чём прикол имеет И что не знаю Причём
Muscovites not Muscovites but Mosk Muscovites
здесь [__] не [__] а Моск [__]
- This means Muscovites are not only
- Это в смысле москвичи не не только
Muscovites, these are
москвичи это
mixed nationalities Yes, who
вот смешанные народности Да которые
lived on the territory of the Moscow
проживали на территории Московской
region,
области
Vologda this Vladimir Ivanovo
Вологодской этой Владимирской Ивановской
right there there  different peoples mixed together Yes, and they
вот там там смешались разные народы Да и
began to speak Russian uh-huh Finno-
начали говорить на русском языке угу
Ugric There were Meryas And why are you
фино угорские Там были меря А вы почему
speaking Russian
почему на русском языке разговариваете
because I wouldn’t speak to you in
пото что не я бы с вами поговорил на
other languages, but you, for example,
других языках но вы например украинский
won’t
не будете
understand Ukrainian who told you we can speak
понимать кто вам сказал можем поговорить
Ukrainian  Why then do you
по-украински Почему вы тогда
speak Russian if you
разговариваете на русском языке если вы
think that means you and yourself are
считаете что значит вы и сам мер
some kind of mer I mean, well, look, if I
какое-то В смысле Ну смотри если я
communicate with an American in
общаюсь с американцем на английском
English, I’m not worth it to Londoners.
языке я же от этого не стою лондонцев
I communicate because he doesn’t know any other way.
Я общаюсь потому что он не знает друго
You know that he’s American  language and
Вы знаете что американский язык и
English - These are almost completely
английский язык - Это совершенно
two different, not completely
практически два разных на не совершенно
two different, but different ones are different, yes,
два разных а разные отличаются да
naturally, because they are already
естественно потому что они уже ско там
developing separately there, it’s logical just
развиваются отдельно это логично также
like Spanish in Spain, Spanish in
как испанский в Испании испанский в
Venezuela Yes, completely different Well, not completely, but
Венесуэле Да совсем разные Ну не совсем
different you think Yes, I don’t think so  I know where
разные думаете Да не думаю я знаю откуда
you were from
вы были
Spanish Say something in
испанский Скажите что-нибудь на
Spanish braid Oh
испанском кос О
God what does it mean with your knowledge of
Господи что значит с твоим знанием
Spanish I could say anything and you
испанско я мог сказать что угодно и ты
would think it was Spanish yes well yes I understand
бы подумал что это испанский
look since you
да понял вот смотрите так как вы кроме
don’t know anything other than Russian so
русского языка ничего не знаете поэтому
I  with you I'm speaking
я с вами Говорю
Russian, let's speak Ukrainian Let's speak
по-русски давайте на украинском Давайте
Ukrainian still two Kishenkova
по-украински ещё таки дву кишенькова
Patelnya Hell knows You see
пательня Да хрен его знает Вот видите
No, you're just speaking your own Speak That's what I'm
Нет вы просто на своём Говорите Так я же
saying Well, if you don't understand not a bunch of
говорю Ну если вы не понимаете не пачка
your own kind of Russian language Well, what the hell I'm
свой род русским языком Ну что сри Я
saying  dvo kishenkova potal, I still don’t
говорю дво кишенькова поталь ё таки не
know, I don’t have to know this, well, how am I going to
знаю не обязан знать это ну как я буду
speak if you don’t understand the words of
говорить если ты не понимаешь слов
our language, just speak it in your own language.
нашего языка просто на своём
I told you, dvo koshe,
говорить Я же тебе говорил вот дво коше
no one,
некого
potal, Alice What is a patelnya
поталь Алиса Что такое
frying pan, dva kishenkova
сковородка дву кишенькова
is not a frying pan,
не
these are stupid  even
сковородка Вот это тупые у них даже
Alice Well, Alice translates them Like two
Алиса Ну Алиса переводит Как как дву
Koshin Kova Patelnya and you melt p ne pa a
кошикова пательня и таете п не па а
p fool without
п дурачок не слыша
even hearing in Ukrainian
даже на украинском
Alice Alice in Ukrainian two Koshin Kova
Алиса Алиса на украинском дву Кошин кова
Patelnya What is a
пательня Что такое
frying pan says one loops of loops
сковородка говорит один петель петель
Ask loops of loops What is in
Спросите петель петель Что такое на
Ukrainian loops What is in
украинском петель Что такое на
Ukrainian loop No no loop loops no
украинском петля Нет не петля петель не
loops skaz loops type e excavator p nya
петель сказа петель типа э экскаватор п
dvo kishenkova name dvo
т ня дво кишенькова имя дво
kishenkova
кишенькова
loops that she’s
петель что она
talking some kind of [ __ ] she’s saying [ __ ]
говорит хуйню какую-то говорит бля
now I’ll ask Ivanka for a frying pan a frying pan is
сейчас я у иванки спрошу
not a frying pan - this is a patel - this
сковорода сковорода не сковорода - это
is a frying pan  p tenya two
п а тель - это сковорода а п теня дву
kishenkova tenya Listen
кишенькова теня Слушай
so Ivanochko say Well in Russian
так иваночко скажи Ну по-русски
please so that the person understands
пожалуйста чтобы человек понял
uh What does two kishenkova tenya mean in Ukrainian
ээ Что означает по-украински дво
Shen of loops is a broken-down
теня Шень петель это раздолбанная
slurp of an
хлебало
orc
орка
funny There are more questions and besides the loops
смешно Ещё вопросы есть а а кроме петель
No give me something else give me more
Нет давай ещё что-нибудь давай ещё
[music  ]
[музыка]
because What
пому Что
is it, translate it into Russian for me
такое переведи мне на на русский язык
now so that Alice now we’ve
сейчас тебе чтоб Алису сейчас мы
uploaded the humovian national tsytsyurnik
загрузили гумовий нацюцюрник
Gondon or something You yourself are a
[__] что ли Сам ты
[ __ ] Listen to the [ __ ] Even Google [ __ ] doesn’t
[__] Слушай бляд Даже Google [__] не
know your
знает твою
body And this is your woman who knows, but apparently it’s not for
тельн А это твоя баба знает да видимо не
use, let’s do it like that
ра пользова давай так
Ivanochka Tell me in  Russian please in
иваночко Скажи по-русски пожалуйста
Russian what does
по-русски что означает в украинском
Gumoviy Natsyutsyurnik
языке гумовий нацюцюрник
Gumoviy na tsu mean in Ukrainian - this is Vladimir
гумовий на ццу - это Владимир
Putin and what does Alice
Путин а Алиса что
say that this is your
говорит что это ваш
master say Ask her
хозяин скажи Спроси её
My Alice is not trained in such a
моя-то не обученная таким
trick Ivanka tell me Who is the master of
фокусом Иванка скажи Кто хозяин
the Russians Putin is the master of the Russians they have
русских Путин - это хозяин русских они у
he is silent
него молчаливые
slaves and you are slaves
рабы а вы рабы
Who is the owner of the Ukrainians
Кто хозяин украинцев
ask
спроси
No you say slaves
Нет вы говорю рабы
are talkative are not needed only in
словоохотливым не нужна только в
emergency cases when I do
экстренных случаях когда у меня своих
n’t
мозгов не
have enough brains now this is a very emergency
хватает сейчас это очень экстренный
case believe me I see I recommend you
случай поверьте я вижу я Рекомендую вам
call
вызывайте
this yarn this is an emergency now it’s
это пря га экстренный сейчас случай вот
just an emergency  it really happens now it’s
просто экстре не бывает реально сейчас
simple Who is the owner of the
просто Кто хозяин
Ukrainians what is she and she she she
украинцев что она го а она она она мне
gives me in short sites
даёт короче сайты
and Turn on the voice Turn on let her say in a voice
и Включите на голос Включите пусть она
she doesn’t
голосом скажет она не
say you speak
говорит ва говори
Alice Who the owner of
Алиса Кто хозяин
the Ukrainians doesn’t
украинцев не
speak gives a link to the site the
говорит даёт ссылку на сайт названы
real owners of Ukraine are named for this
настоящие владельцы Украины вот на эту
crap
хуйню
they give you how to do
дают как вам
this Now I’ll ask
такое Сейчас я спрошу
uh
ээ
Ivanka Please tell me in Russian so that
Иванка Скажи пожалуйста по-русски чтобы
the person I’m talking to can understand who is the
человек мой с которым я говорю понял Кто
master of
хозяин
the Ukrainians, the Ukrainians have no master, they are
украинцев у украинцев нет хозяина они
free people and the Russians are silent slaves,
вольные люди а россияне безмолвные рабы
even Alice is afraid to
у них даже Алиса боится
speak What a
говорить Какая
delight, how can I download such an Ivanka
прелесть как мне закачать такую иванку
?  -well,
ну-ка
she’s banned by Roskomnadzor, you
а она же забанена Роскомнадзор её за
have to log in behind her and use a Ukrainian
надо спина заходить и под украинским
phone number. Why don’t we have anything new?
номером телефона Да что ж у нас нов нет
Why don’t we have tacos, where is it like Ivanka, where is
Да что е нету тако где как Иванка где
it, what is it
это как она
called? How to download
называется Как скачать
Ivanka
иванку
voice, you have to write in Ukrainian
голосовой надо по-украински писать
voice pomichnik
голосовый помичник
Ivanka Yes, you don’t need to write anything in Ukrainian,
Иванка Да не надо ничего по-украински
it won’t download in Ukrainian,
писать она так не скачается по-украински
she has protection from Russians,
у неё защита от русских
something is missing because in the
стоит что-то нету потому что на
Ukrainian language Now I’ll ask Ivanka how to
украинском языке Сейчас я иванку спрошу
download Ivanka from Russia
как из России скачать
and this is some kind of patriotic thing so that
а это какая-то патриотична штука чтобы
you don’t have a complex No, this is a development of
вы не комплексовать Нет это ж разработка
Google
Google Да ладно
Come on, Dani is not for the Ukrainian audience Well, something is screwed up and impoverishes
Ну капец что-то нищает
Google, come
Google
on, say something else that we are
а ну давай Ещё что-нибудь скажи что мы
all slaves there and other crap and this is
тут все рабы там и прочую хуйню а это
very funny Let’s do it now as you
очень Забавно Давай сейчас как как вы
want  How to download Ivanka Yes, this is
хотите Как скачать иванку Да из это
Ivanka Please tell me how a person from
Иванка Скажи пожалуйста как человеку из
Russia can download you to his phone in
России скачать тебя к себе на телефон в
Russia under a Russian
России под российским
provider You can’t download Ivanka from Russia
провайдером из России иванку не скачаешь
because Ivanka is free and slaves
потому что Иванка свободная а рабам
are not entitled to Freedom
Свобода не положена
very
очень
nice And ask Ivanka And who is
мило А спроси иванку А кто сейчас
supporting
содержит
Ukraine now by the way  you laugh, it
Украину ещё кстати вот вы смеётесь у
has a facial analysis function,
него есть функция анализа по лицу вот
look now Ivanka
смотрите сейчас Иванка Посмотри
Please look at this interlocutor of mine and
пожалуйста на этого моего собеседника и
you can recognize his face if
Распознай его лицо можешь если
you determine who it is
определишь кто это
please This is some kind of fabulous eating
пожалуйста Это какой-то сказочный жрущий
hamster Damn Ivanochko you have humor
хомяк Блин иваночко у тебя юмор
of course Ivanochko Ask Who is supporting now
конечно у иваночко Спросите А кто сейчас
Ukraine
Украину
[music]
[музыка]
now it feels like you are typing
сейчас такое ощущение что Вы печатаете
your
ваши
Ivanka, what what to ask again who
Иванка что что ещё раз спросить кто
now supports Ukraine Ivanka who
сейчас содержит Украину Иванка кто
now supports Ukraine Ukraine contains
сейчас содержит Украину Украину содержит
the whole world and Russia
весь мир а Россия
now
теперь
Well, on this positive note that
Ну вот на этой позитивной ноте что вас
the whole world supports you,
содержит весь мир с вами
I say
содержа я
goodbye to you
прощаюсь
[  music]
[музыка]
[laughter]
[смех]
Come on type
Давай типаж
Prik Damn I don’t write on my Telegram right
прик Блин я не пись на мий Telegram прям
now axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ORV in your ban and even
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people often I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that  Shchob mi Mali operational link write
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок пиши
directly immediately and while there in telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video schezh
видео ще теж
tsikava and korisna information and we are guilty
цикава и корисна информация и мы повинни
of you trimati postiyny operational
з вами тримати постийний оперативный
link
звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write
пиши